const questions = [{
    question: "What is responsible for charging the battery?",
    choices: ["Compressor", "Alternator", "Water Pump", "Flux Capacitor"],
    correctAnswer: "Alternator",
  },
  {
    question: "A _____ is a type of forced induction compressor.",
    choices: ["Turbocharger", "Water Pump", "Generator", "Transmission"],
    correctAnswer: "Turbocharger",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is in charge of cooling the fluid that runs through the engine?",
    choices: ["Amplifier", "Air Intake", "Radiator", "Carburetor"],
    correctAnswer: "Radiator",
  },
  {
    question: "A _____ can be drilled or slotted to dissipate heat better.",
    choices: ["Brake Rotor", "Harmonic Balancer", "Fan Pulley", "Wheel Bearing"],
    correctAnswer: "Brake Rotor",
  },
  {
    question: "There is usually one of these in every cylinder of a modern engine.",
    choices: ["Lock Actuator", "Temperature Sensor", "Throttle Solenoid", "Fuel Injector"],
    correctAnswer: "Fuel Injector",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following receives electricty from an ignition coil?",
    choices: ["Fuel Sensor", "Spark Plug", "Piston Actuator", "Heater Filament"],
    correctAnswer: "Spark Plug",
  },
  {
    question: "A _____ must be balanced in order to function properly.",
    choices: ["Driveshaft", "Air Filter", "Starter Cover", "Exhaust Clamp"],
    correctAnswer: "Driveshaft",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following has a gear that pops out and rotates the flywheel when energized?",
    choices: ["Water Solenoid", "Trunk Actuator", "Alternator", "Starter"],
    correctAnswer: "Starter",
  },
  {
    question: "A _____ controls one electrical circuit by opening and closing contacts in another circuit.",
    choices: ["Relay", "Fuse", "Backup Battery", "Oxygen Sensor"],
    correctAnswer: "Relay",
  },
  {
    question: "What is used to convert carbon dioxide to carbon monoxide?",
    choices: ["Coolant Filter", "A/C Condenser", "Catalytic Converter", "Axle Shaft"],
    correctAnswer: "Catalytic Converter",
  },
]